// ________FAKE_DATA_______________
let questions = [
  {
    quiz_id: 1,
    question:
      "You can learn a lot about the local _______ by talking to local people.",
    answers: ["territory", "area", "land", "nation"],
  },
  {
    quiz_id: 2,
    question:
      "It's good to have someone to ________ you when you are visiting a new place.",
    answers: ["lead", "take", "guide", "bring"],
  },
  {
    quiz_id: 3,
    question:
      "When you ______ your destination, your tour guide will meet you at the airport.",
    answers: ["arrive", "reach", "get", "achieve"],
  },
  {
    quiz_id: 4,
    question: "It can be quite busy here during the tourist ______",
    answers: ["season", "phase", "period", "stage"],
  },
  {
    quiz_id: 5,
    question:
      "Make sure you _______ a hotel before you come to our island, especially in the summer.",
    answers: ["book", "keep", "put", "buy"],
  },
  {
    quiz_id: 6,
    question: "Captain Cook discovered Australia on a _______ to the Pacific.",
    answers: ["vacation", "travel", "cruise", "voyage"],
  },
  {
    quiz_id: 7,
    question:
      " Most tourist attractions in London charge an admission ________.",
    answers: ["fare", "ticket", "fee", "pay"],
  },
  {
    quiz_id: 8,
    question: "The hotel where we are _______ is quite luxurious.",
    answers: ["living", "existing", "remaining", "staying"],
  },
  {
    quiz_id: 9,
    question: "Is English an ________ language in your country?",
    answers: ["mother", "official", "living", "old"],
  },
  {
    quiz_id: 10,
    question: "He spoke a ______ of French that we found hard to understand.",
    answers: ["slang", "jargon", "dialect", "language"],
  },
];
const results = [
  {
    quiz_id: 1,
    answer: "area",
  },
  {
    quiz_id: 3,
    answer: "reach",
  },
  {
    quiz_id: 2,
    answer: "guide",
  },
  {
    quiz_id: 4,
    answer: "season",
  },
  {
    quiz_id: 5,
    answer: "book",
  },
  {
    quiz_id: 6,
    answer: "voyage",
  },
  {
    quiz_id: 7,
    answer: "fee",
  },
  {
    quiz_id: 8,
    answer: "staying",
  },
  {
    quiz_id: 9,
    answer: "official",
  },
  {
    quiz_id: 10,
    answer: "dialect",
  },
];
